It's crazy. Finally, I was able to support fully
transparent videos in fframes.
This situation with transparent video is ridiculously
bad on the web and basically anything supports
it correctly. It's madness. WebM, VP9 codec with
transparency mode, does not actually behave
like it is a transparency mode just stores the alpha
channel separately. There is hevc (h265)
with support for the alpha channel which doesn't work
either because you need a specific build
of hevc encoder to actually have support of the alpha
channel. There is Apple ProRes which actually
supports alpha channel correctly but it is
Apple's vendor-locked codec and basically it is a nightmare and
surprisingly fframes already supports them all
out of the box and just works fine. I am SUPER excited